

TRAN THI TU LINH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+84-353-544-089

tranthitulinh1305@gmail.com

my-portfolio-mni-linh.vercel.app/

Oistrict 11, Ho Chi Minh City

HCM University of Education

2019 - 5/2023 Software Engineering GPA: 3.26/4.00

EDUCATION

Transcript: https://ibb.co/3vm3HjS

SKILLS

- Front-end development with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Atomic Design, Bootstrap, MUI, ReactJS, Redux, Responsive website.
- · Knowledge of UI/UX.
- Work with RESTful API.
- Using Git and GitHub.
- Using Figma, Postman, Power BI.

CERTIFICATIONS

Agile & Scrum Training | Dek
Technologies Vietnam | Nov 2021

https://ibb.co/r47DZZt

ABOUT ME

I'm a front-end developer with 1 year of experience and I want to find a full-time job. My career goal is to apply and improve programming skills and participate in real corporate projects as a front-end developer as well as have the opportunity to be exposed to a The further position is full stack developer.

EXPERIENCE



Hahalolo Travel Social Network

Fresher Front-end Developer

May 2022 - May 2023

- Backend, handnote, vendor report, products comparison page of the tour, car rental, plane ticket, seller info, affiliate marketing.
 - Determining the structure and design of web pages.
- Write code for the user interface, maintaining and modifying websites.
- Ensuring responsive websites are accessible across many platforms, including laptops and smartphones.
 - Build reusable code for future use.
 - Fixing website issues and bugs that arise.

Fresher Data Analyst

Feb 2022 - May 2022

- Newsfeed Hahalolo, Missword, SeaGame
 - Indentifying data sources, collecting data, sourcing missing data.
 - Analysing data to find answers to specific questions.
 - Developing, implementing and maintaining databases.
- Assessing quality of data, indentifying trends, removing and cleaning data.
 - Preparing reports for executive and project teams.
 - Createing visualisation of data.
 - Write automated interactive tools.

Hotel, plane ticket, car rental, tour

- Proposing promotion formula
- Prepare and generate reports on the number of customers interested and purchasing trends.



TRAN THI TU LINH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

HONOURS & AWARDS

Student Scientific Research Awards | Consolation Prize at School level

HCM University of Education [2021]

- Topic: Building Face Mask Detection System.
- https://urlvn.net/ufrgvv

Student Scientific Research Awards | The Third Prize at School level

HCM University of Education [2021]

- · Topic: Building a system of identification of fruits in the import-export and counting stages.
- https://urlvn.net/pbm94o

EXPERIENCE

Subject project at HCM University of Education

Data Structures

Sep 2021 - Oct 2021

- Description: AVL tree visualization application.
- My position: Design UI and write code that implements the function:
 - Tree Traversals (NLR, LNR, LRN)
- Redraw the balanced tree knowing the results of the NLR, LNR, and LRN traversal.

Search, Add/Delete node and tree balance.

- Technology used: HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- Link github: https://github.com/mni-linh/Report-Subject-Datastructure

Web Technology

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021

- Description: This is an e-commerce project. The website sells watercolors and some hand-painted paintings.
- My position: Design UI and write interface code for Client and Admin.
- Client including Sign up, Sign in, Home page, Course sale page, Product page, Contact page, Shopping Cart, Checkout page.
- Admin including Sign up, Sign in, Statistics page, List and Customer Information, Product List, Order List and Register page an account for employees
- Technology used: HTML, CSS, SCSS, Javascript, ReactJS, Bootstrap.
- · Link github:
 - Client: https://github.com/mni-linh/hama-fe
 - Admin: https://github.com/mni-linh/hama-admin
- · Link website:
 - Client: https://hamacorner.vercel.app/
 - Admin: https://hama-admin.vercel.app/
 - + username: tranthitulinh1305@gmail.com
 - + password: 281123